= kisskh.lv =
Was it good?
Damn you.
You're too old for wet dreams.
Shut up. Why are you here?
[Red Ginseng Extract]
Here, for you.
Hey.
Was it that good?
Get lost.
Why? Who did you dream of?
What did you do?
Sure you should take that?
Won't you get even more hot and bothered?
What are you doing?
Why?
Want to see what that feels like?
You're crazy.
My mom bought some for you
while buying it for my dad.
She said to drink one pouch a day.
Are you her son or am I?
Your mom said that?
That's right.
At this rate,
she might as well be your mom.
Want one?
I don't need your charity.
Drink it all
and get into Seoul National University.
Tell your mom I said thanks.
Tell her yourself.
You're basically her son!
According to solar terms,
we've officially crossed the threshold
into summer.
It'll be mostly sunny
across the country today,
with daytime temperatures soaring
and bringing blistering heat everywhere.
As temperatures rise sharply,
please pay attention to food safety
to prevent food poisoning.
Fair and dry conditions will persist
for the foreseeable future,
with no major rainfall expected.
[Sung Inho]
[Kim Domin]
[Summertime]
[Choi Gunwoo: My girlfriend and I
finally kissed yesterday.]
[Seo Jaewon: Congrats.]
[Yoo Wonho: That'll be me soon.]
[Choi Gunwoo: You don't even
have a girlfriend, idiot. Lol.]
[Seo Jaewon: How was it? Was it good?]
Hey, Cha Dohyun.
Have you ever kissed before?
What?
You must have, right?
Was it good?
Oh, right.
You kissed just now too, didn't you?
Smooching in your dream.
How was it? Tell me!
If you wanna know, try it yourself.
With whom?
Sigh, you know
there are no girls around me.
Gosh, I can't wait for my first kiss.
Any cute girls you can hook me up with?
I'm quite a catch myself, aren't I?
Yeo Eunho,
who could handle you?
What?
Cha Dohyun, what do you know?
Have you dated me?
Have you?
Damn it, it's the vice principal.
Haven't seen him in a while.
Well, students should wear uniforms,
all neat and tidy.
Hey, take your top off.
You won't get scolded anyway.
The teachers all like you.
They like me because I wear my uniform.
Are you even a friend?
Of course we're friends.
What else could we be?
Let's swap clothes.
You're too tiny.
Hey, we're about the same size, okay?
Even if you show up naked,
you won't get in trouble.
Okay?
What's in it for me?
Seriously?
Forget it, then.
Okay. What do you want in return?
You changed your home passcode again.
It's because you
keep coming over all the time...
Hey, fine.
I'll go distract the vice principal.
Here I go.
It's you, Dohyun!
I heard you're getting an award this time.
I just paid attention in class.
It's all thanks to the teachers' guidance.
You're such a sweet kid.
Stop right there.
Yeo Eunho,
where are you going in such a hurry?
You rascal. Get over here!
Y-You...
Didn't I tell you to dress properly
in your uniform?
Let's talk this out.
Talk this out? Do you listen?
Wait...
Why's your hair still that color?
It's naturally brown.
I was born with brown hair.
Naturally brown?
You and your excuses!
You brat!
You punk!
You rascal! You...
You're really testing my patience.
It's not mine!
Gosh, you punk...
Yes, Dohyun, go on in.
Cha Dohyun, I'm going to kill you!
I'll kill you first. Come here!
Turn around!
Run!
You too! Run!
It's so freaking hot.
It's summer.
Summer already?
Yoo Wonho, have you been working out?
Check out my guns.
-Woah, insane.
-What am I looking at?
I told you to take the red ginseng.
You traitor.
And stop smoking.
I said those cigarettes aren't mine.
You know I hate the smell of smoke.
How did a pack suddenly fall out?
Hey, Cha Dohyun, do you...
Bye.
Hey, was it yours? Was it?
Hey!
Yeo Eunho, hurry up.
Jerk.
Psycho.
Total lunatic.
Academic Excellence Award.
Cha Dohyun of Year 3, Class 3
has shown exceptional academic performance
and excellent conduct.
As an exemplary role model,
he is hereby awarded this certificate.
July 4, 2025.
This was Hwang Sungyu,
Principal of Ohbok High School.
Psycho.
A freaking athlete with excellent grades.
He's basically a cheat code, huh?
So sickening.
It's creepy how flawless he is.
Could he be small down there?
You mean this small.
Yeo Eunho, you must've seen it.
It's small, right?
It has to be small.
Eunho.
You grew up with him. I'm sure you know.
Is it this small?
What's with him?
Damn it.
Even after 19 years,
I still can't figure him out.
[3 years ago]
In our third year of middle school,
I saved up my allowance
to buy a game console.
The thing is, single-player games
were popular back then.
In those days, our fiercest rivalry
was the daily
race home from school.
Long story short,
the loser was always...
Damn it.
Always me.
Is this your home?
Are you kidding me?
I only wore that shirt once.
Hey, take it off.
Take it off! Now, now, now!
You're so noisy.
My dad and his dad were
high school classmates.
They got married around the same time
and settled down in the same neighborhood.
Just like that, we've been living
in the same neighborhood for 19 years.
That is, since we
started walking in diapers,
we've never been apart.
Time out.
Idiot.
You'll never pass that level.
You've been stuck for a month.
You win.
Eunho.
I always get what I want.
What the hell are you talking about?
Your slump and injuries
were all lies, right?
You're actually fine, right?
I knew something was off.
You've been wearing that cast for a month.
I'm quitting
taekwondo.
What? Are you crazy?
What are you going to do
if you quit taekwondo?
Study.
You?
Do you think...
I can't do it?
Psycho.
A total lunatic.
To reiterate,
Cha Dohyun's determination and tenacity
are beyond anyone's imagination.
In all my 19 years,
I've never seen another
persistent psycho like him.
Is this a diss? Why give this to me?
Let's go to the snack shop. Your treat.
You won the award.
Why's it my treat?
It should be your treat.
What's an athlete like you
being so studious for?
What's this?
Damn it. Let's run!
What—
Shh.
Damn it, I just washed my shoes yesterday.
Ugh, I hate this.
Hey, do you have tissues?
Damn it. That's why I had that dream.
[Summertime]
We have a new transfer student.
Are you two close?
Yup.
I'm his only friend.
We're childhood friends by circumstance.
Childhood friends by circumstance, huh?
Did you catch a cold
from the rain yesterd—
Don't touch me.
[Yeo Eunho]
Does he really not know,
or is he just pretending?
Shut up.
Tell me.
Is it yours?
You like Yeo Eunho, don't you?
If not, can I like him?
Do you like me?
Back off.
He...
is mine.